eboomwebsolutions.com 2018-09-30

# Web Design Company Vancouver BC Canada

Building the success of your online business... 

Privacy Policy  

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**Privacy Statement** – All information gathered by E-Boom Web Solutions is considered personal information and not shared. We believe that this information deserves protection. The personal information submitted to E-Boom Web Solutions via web forms or electronic correspondence is collected for the sole purpose of processing your requests and orders.  
E-Boom Web Solutions respects the privacy of every individual who visits our website. It is our policy not to distribute, sell, rent or in any way make available, your name, e-mail address or any other personally identifiable information to any third party, advertisers, business partners, sponsors, etc., for marketing purposes. We certify that we will not share or sell your personal information without explicit permission or consent.  

**If you visit our website:**  
In general, you can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. 

Any personal information that may be collected via our web site is collected in compliance with section 32(c) of the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy (FOIP) Act. 

The information collected is limited to what is necessary for system administration and includes such things as :

**Server Data** – Our servers generate statistical logs that contain the following information:   
• Internet address of computer being used  
• Web pages requested  
• Referring Web page  
• Browser used  
• Date and Time  

**How the information is used** – We use the information you provide for the purpose of assessing our information services and in order to :   
• Fulfill requests for products, services or information about products or services.  
• Provide customer services.  
• Manage contests or promotions.  
• Offer new products and services.

For example, we request personal information when you set up an account online, purchase products, participate in a sweepstakes, promotion or survey.   

When you participate in site features such as newsletters, specials, promotions, contests, etc., Our list is an opt in list, that means you will not receive any newsletter without confirming your subscription. You may unsubscribe at any time you wish.

Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, court order, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law.  
We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful. We may release certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.   

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or use of your information, please contact us at: webmaster@eboomwebsolutions.com or by mail at:

E-Boom Web Solutions   
Suite 628  
101-1001 West Broadway  
Vancouver, B.C.  
V6H 4E
